pctechbytes.com 2011-08-09

# Disclaimer and Privacy Policy

**Disclaimer**

PCTechBytes is not responsible for the destruction of your personal property or any harm that comes to you through use of advice or information contained on our site and we will not be held liable for any damages. You understand that computer repair or maintenance is to be performed only by a certified technician.

Since this is a community-based environment, there are a lot of opinions expressed about products, companies and services. Their opinions may be those of our members, but do not reflect our own. If you find a post on our boards that is damaging to you or your business, please notify us and we will immediately review it, and remove it if necessary. 

**PCTechBytes, LLC Privacy Policy**

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
PCTechBytes, LLC Company is committed to protecting your personal privacy. We provide this notice to explain the type of information we collect on Web sites owned by the PCTechBytes, LLC Company (www.pctechbytes.com) and how we use this information. Our Privacy Policy is available for you to review on the home page of every PCTechBytes, LLC Web site. 

**The Information We Collect**  
You may be asked to provide personal information to participate in programs or features of the site. These may include but are not limited to coupons, contests, surveys, forums and/or subscription. Your participation is voluntary and we will not require you to provide more information than is necessary to participate in any of our current or future Web site activities. In some instances, we may ask you questions on an aggregate basis (we don't identify you personally with the information) and such questions will be identified on the Web site. In all other instances, you should assume that we will track any information you provide on a personally identifiable basis. 

**Parents and children**  
PCTechBytes, LLC Company does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Children ages 13 to 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on PCTechBytes, LLC Company sites. 

**The Way We Use Information**  
PCTechBytes, LLC Company Web sites may provide you with the opportunity to register on the site. Registration may be required to be eligible to receive savings offers, enter online contests or sweepstakes or receive specialized content. PCTechBytes, LLC Company may use the information you provide when registering to fulfill prizes.

When you register with our Web site, you may elect to receive information and updates on our products and services. You will always have an opportunity to decline receiving such communications.

We might use information you provide to better design our Web site and improve our marketing and our products. One method through which this Web site collects aggregate information is the collection of IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. Web servers, the computers that "serve up" Web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from this Web site, our servers may log your IP address. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so.

**Unsubscribe/Delete**  
PCTechBytes, LLC gives users the following options for managing or removing their information from our database:

1\. Send us an email: Send an email to pctechbytes@gmail.com. Be sure to include your name and clear instructions on what you would like us to do. 

**Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are files or bits of information that may be stored in your computer's hard drive when you visit a Web site. We may use cookies to better tailor our site and our products to your interests and needs. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not voluntarily provided by you. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most Web sites. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent so that you can flush them from your browser if you object to their presence. 

Our Privacy Practices with Third Parties We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. We do not provide any identifiable personal information to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless you register or subscribe for their services.

Our intention is never to use or share personally identifiable information provided to us in ways that are different than the ways described above without also providing you with an opportunity to "unsubscribe" or prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx ](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
You should be aware that when you are on PCTechBytes, LLC Web sites you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There may be links to other sites that take you outside our service. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that may use the PCTechBytes, LLC logo. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. Check the linked site to locate its Privacy Policy, which may be different from our own. If the PCTechBytes, LLC Web site links you to any third party Web site, PCTechBytes, LLC makes no representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of its Privacy Policy. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security:**  
We take reasonable precautions to keep your personal information private and secure. However, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk. 

**Changes in Our Policy**  
We reserve the right to modify or remove this Policy at our discretion. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post those changes here. You should visit this area frequently to stay informed.

**Your Consent To This Privacy Policy**  
By using this Web site, you signify your assent to the PCTechBytes, LLC Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not use this site or submit any personally identifiable information

**Second-Party Links Disclaimer**

We provide links to web sites operated by other parties. The links are provided for your convenience only. The presence of a link does not imply any endorsement of the material on the web sites, nor does it imply any association with the web site's operators. We do not control or endorse any information, products or services provided by third parties through these links. We are not responsible for the content and performance of these sites. Use of linked sites is strictly at your own risk including any risks associated with destructive viruses.

**Copyright**

All articles on PCTechBytes are protected under Copyright laws. Articles may not be reproduced without permission. If our content is stolen, we will take legal action. While we do allow syndication on our forums, these articles are not to reproduced without permission. 

Return to pctechbytes
